Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Zheng, Jie-min
    - Zheng, Jie-min [also as Cheng Chieh-min] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 12/10/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 69)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, page 36 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zheng Jie-min [also as Cheng Chieh-ming], [Kaohsiung] 14/3/[n.y.], (1 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 69.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zheng Jie-min, [n.p.] 8/11//[n.y.], (1 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 69.01)
  - Zheng, Yu-xiu
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Zheng Yu-xiu [also as Mme Wei Dao-ming, Cheng Yu- hsiu], [n.p.] 18/12/[n.y.], (2 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 70.01)
    - Zheng, Yu-xiu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 card ) (Box 04, Folder 70.01)
  - Zhou, Cong-zheng
    - Zhou, Cong-zheng [also as Chou Tsung-cheng] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 24/2/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 71)
  - Zhou, Jing-wen
    - Zhou, Jing-wen et al To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 20/2/[n.y.], (1 page, telegram ) (Box 06, Folder 07)
      [See Telegrams after Xi An [Box 6 Folder 15]: With 15 people, Listed: Wang Zhuo-ran, Song Xing-ta, Chen Xian-zhou, Ye Bi-liang, Yu Cheng-ze, Zhou Jing-wen, Wu Ou, Yang Wei-zhen, Du Qi-jie, Li Xi-geng, Zhang Ke-wei, Han Li-ru, Tian Yu-shi, Wang Chong-yu, Wang Guan-wu]
  - Zhou Lian-hua
    - (Box 04, Folder 72-73)
      [Note; see under L. H. Chow]
  - Zhou, Yi -ou
    - Zhou, Yi -ou [also as Chow Yi-ou] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 74)
  - Zhu, Hui-ji
    - Zhu, Hui-ji To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 16/10/1990, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 09.06)
  - Zhu Lian-qing
    - Wei, De-tang [also as Wei The-t’ang] and Zhu Lian-qing To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chu Lian-ch’ing], (1page,autographlettersigned/[n.p.]8/5/[n.y.] ) (Box 04, Folder 75)
  - Zhu, Shou-en
    - Zhu, Shou-en To Peter H. L. Chang, Sichuan 1/3/1990, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 01.12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - The Alumni General Association of the Northeastern University To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang, China, December 1992, (Christmas card and 4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 35, Folder 01.09)
    - Chih-yu Ho To Edith Chao Chang, [Hawaii] 25/10/1996, (1 page, autograph letter (photocopy) ) (Box 05, Folder 03)
    - [?] To H.L.Chang, [n.p.], may 18 [n.y.], (1 page autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 15)
    - Li Li-Lu[?] To H.H. Chang, Koyoto, July 31, 1970, (2 page autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 18.01)
    - [?] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Shanghai] 5/11/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 01, Folder 01)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 66-67 ]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To (?) Gong Xia, [Xikou] 19/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 12.01)
    - [Various People] To [Peter H. L. Chang?], [v.p.], 1937-1939, (17 telegrams ) (Box 06, Folder 17)
    - [Various People] To [v.p., including Chang], [v.p.], 1960s, (21 items (one with attached 3 sheets) and 1 general list with 2 medical lists ) (Box 06, Folder 18)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. 21 empty envelopes addresses to Peter H. L. Chang, [various places and dates] (Box 33, Folder 04)
    - Thank You Note, [n.p.] December 24, 1998, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.01)
    - Miscellaneous Note, [n.p.] April 6 [n. y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.01)
    - Proof of Receipt, [n.p.] December 24 [n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.02)
- Series II: Manuscripts
  - Subseries 2.1: Peter Chang
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Letter to President Chiang Kai-shek on "Recollection of Xian Incident. [Memory]-A Draft ". The whole document is a letter. "Recollection" is the main body of this Letter., Jingshang, 5-6 December 1956, (44 page autograph manuscript (draft ) ) (Box 07, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Ten additional pages to the "Letter to President Chiang Kai-shek on 'Recollection of Xian Incident [Memory]-A Draft'"., Jingshang, 17 December [1956], (10 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 01.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Reviewed version of "Letter to President Chiang Kai-shek on 'Recollection of Xian Incident [Memory]-A Draft'", Jingshang, [10 May 1957], (43 page manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 01.03)
      [ The review was instructed by Chiang Kai-shek]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Revised version of "Letter to President Chiang Kai-shek on 'Recollection of Xian Incident [Memory]-A Draft'", Jingshang, [n.d.], (54 page manuscript (draft) and note ) (Box 07, Folder 01.04)
      [This version incorporated reviewer’s notations.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Two-page addition to the reviewed version of "Letter to President Chiang Kai- shek on 'Recollection of Xian Incident [Memory]-A Draft'", Jingshang, [n.d.], (2 page manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 01.05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Painful Lessons from Xian Incident - An Open Letter., Jingshang, 24 August 1958, (41 page, autograph manuscript (first draft) ) (Box 07, Folder 01.06)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Letter to President Chiang Kai-shek on "Miscellaneous recollections", an autobiographical account of Peter H. L. Chang, Jingshang, 22 April 1957, (2 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: Table of Contents Manuscript of proposed Autobiography, Jingshang, January-April 1957, (8 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.02)
      [Note: With notes (recording of bits and pieces of phrasing reference or other references) on three pieces of paper.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: Preface and Afterward of poposed Autobiography, Jingshang, January-April 1957, (10 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.03)
      [Note: Preface: First draft 2p; Second draft 2p and final clear copy 2p. Afterward: Draft only 4p.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: My father and my ancestors-Chapter I of Proposed Autobiography, Jingshang, 14 January-April 1946, (116 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.04)
      [Note: First draft 32p;Second draft 42p and final clear copy 41p]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: My Early Years-Chapter 2 of Proposed Autobiography, Jingshang, 21 January 1957, (40 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.05)
      [Note: First draft 20p;Final clear copy 20p]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: Launching a Military career-Chapter 3 of Proposed Autobiography, Jingshang, [n.d.], (31 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.06)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: Major Military Campaigns-Chaptert 4 of Proposed Autobiography, Jingshang, [n.d.], (50 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.07)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: Kuomintang and I-Chapter 5 of Proposed Autobiography, Jingshang, [n.d.], (8 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.08)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: My Understanding of the Chinese Communist Party [Chapter 6 of proposed Autobiography], Jingshang, [n.d.], (15 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.09)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Recollections: From my trip abroad to my house arrest [Chapter 7 of Proposed Autobiography], Jingshang, [n.d.], (42 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 02.10)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Autobiography(Draft), [n.p., n.d.], (2 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 03.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Autobiography, Jingshang, [n.d.], (169 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 03.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. A single page about the Communist Party of China, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 03.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Comments on "Soviet Russia in China", Jingshang, 19 August 1957, (24 page autograph manuscript (draft, carbon) ) (Box 07, Folder 04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Story of Two Pilots, [Taiwan], 15 May 1982, (9 page autograph manuscript draft) (Box 07, Folder 05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mr.. Liu Yi-guang (On Christianity), [Taiwan, n.d.], (3 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 06)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Statement to Lytton Commission, Peiping, April 1932, (12 page, typed manuscript (photocopy) ) (Box 07, Folder 07)
      [Note: Confidential]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. How I became a Christian. Testimony, Chinese and English, USA, [1994-96], (9 page, typed manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 08)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Poetry, [n.p., n.d.], (14 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 09.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Favorite Poems by Others, [n.p., n.d.], (4 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 09.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Jacob and Chinese Traditional Philosophy, [n.p., n.d.], (86 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 10.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Jacob and Chinese Traditional Philosophy (first draft), [n.p., n.d.], (26 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 10.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Jacob and Chinese Traditional Philosophy (Misc. Notes), [n.p., n.d.], (54 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 10.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Writing Notes, [n.p., v.d], (4 page autograph manuscript, 3/4/ 1936; 1 page, autograph manuscript, 4/1940; 1 page, autograph manuscript, 2/3/1942; 2 page, autograph manuscript, 23/5/1942; 2 page, autograph manuscript, 27/8/1942 ) (Box 07, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Writing Notes, [n.p., n.d.], (4 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 11.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Writing Notes, [n. p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 11.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Writing Notes, [n. p., n.d.], (5 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 11.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Writing Notes, [n.p., n.d.], (5 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 11.05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Readings Reflections, [n.p., v.d], (9 p autograph manuscript, and 1 page, autograph manuscript 31/7/1957. ) (Box 07, Folder 12.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Du Daxue Zhaji, Xiziwan, 2/4/1959, (79 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 12.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes (about Western Affairs), [n.p., n.d.], (28 page autograph manuscript in two loose packets of 7 and 21 page respectively. ) (Box 07, Folder 13)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes of US Political Parties and Elections, [n.p., n.d.], (21 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 13.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Quotations From Western Philosophers, [n. p., n.d.], (3 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 13.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. History of the U.S.A., [n.p., n.d.], (32 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 13.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Zhu Cun Lu (Study Notes), [n.p., n.d.], (13 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 07, Folder 14)
    - Chang, Peter H. L.? Outline of the Record of the Xian Incident, [n.p., n.d.], (4 printed pages numbered 12-15-photocopies ) (Box 07, Folder 15.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Notes on Confucius Readings. [n.p., n.d.], (8 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 01)
      [With 1 piece of news clipping, and 1page of Confucius quotation in English.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Dao, [n.p., n.d.], (10 page autograph manuscript 1 v.(b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Ren, [n.p., n.d.], (19 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Ren, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page, autograph manuscript 1 v. .(b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Ru, [n.p., n.d.], (12 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Shi, [n.p., n.d.], (5 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Shu, [n.p., n.d.], (5 page, autograph manuscript 1 v. .(b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Xue, [n.p., n.d.], (22 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Yi, [n.p., n.d.], (5 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Zheng-ming, [n.p., n.d.], (4 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Zhong, [n.p., n.d.], (3 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. [Ge-Yan] I, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript 1 v.(b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. [Ge-Yan] II, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b. d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. [Ge-Yan] III, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Ming Ci Shi Yi, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Lun Li, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Guanyu Rujia de Xinde, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Li, [n.p., n.d.], (25 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Du Rushu Beiwanglu, [n.p.] [v.d. /1947], (12 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Du Xun Zha Ji, [n.p.] 23 December 1945, (6 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Zheng, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Dushu Ji Yi, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Guanyu Xin and Xing wenti, [n.p.] 1 and 2 June 1946, (5 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Mingyan Zhaiji, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b. d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Xiziwan Dushu Zhaji, Xiziwan [n.d.], (5 page autograph manuscript 1 v. (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Misc. Quotations from famous people, [n.p., n.d.], (1 note book (22 pages) and 3 page autograph manuscript signed ) (Box 08, Folder 04.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Motto, [n.p., n.d.], (4 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 04.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Motto, [n.p.] 4/4/1953, (2 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 04.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Copying of Liang Qichao’s "Tan Sitong Zhuan Houlun", [n.p.] 26 May 1947, (3 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Copying, by Edith C. Chang, Tan Sitong’s "Xing E Pian", [n.p., n.d.], (26 page manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Copying, by Edith C. Chang, of "Shidalin Gongzuo de Fangfa he Shidalin Lun Zhenglue he Zhengce", [n.p., n.d.], (11 page manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Name List of Peiping Political Consultative Council, [n.p.] 21 June [n.y.], (2 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Name Lists of The Seventh National Congress of the Chinese Communist Party and other Chinese Political Parties and Organizations, [n.p., n.d.], (18 page manuscript [Edith Chang handwriting] ) (Box 08, Folder 05.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Notes on Medication, [n.p., n.d.], (14 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Copying of "Introduction to Japanese Militarism", Jingshang, July 1951, (88 page autograph manuscript (b.d. copy) ) (Box 08, Folder 05.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Notes on Misc. Readings: On "Chinese Traditional Culture" by Zhu Ben-yuan, Yang mingdong, [n.d.], (1 page autograph manuscript (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 05.05)
      [Note; in same volume as following 7.p.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Geographical Notes on Southern Guizhou, [n.p., n.d.], (7 page autograph manuscript (b.d.) ) (Box 08, Folder 05.05)
    - [Chang, Peter H. L.] High Fidelity System Instructions, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.06)
      [With Stanley E. Henning’s Name Card]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. This and That: Names of books and people, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 05.07)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. How To Catch Pike, [n.p.] [n.d.], (7 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 06.01)
      [Note: same volume as following entry]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. On New Punctuation, [n.p., n.d.], (22 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 08, Folder 06.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous cards and notes, 7 pieces (Box 08, Folder 07.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Copy of original book " The Sure Victory," By Mei-Ling Soong Chang, London, Glasgow, and Westwood, New Jersey, 1955, (45 pages and note ) (Box 09, Folder 01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang (pp. 1-25), [n.p., n.d.], (48 page manuscript draft) (Box 09, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang (pp. 1-7), [n.p., n.d.], (14 page manuscript draft) (Box 09, Folder 01.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang (pp.10-17), [n.p., n.d.], (15 page manuscript (draft, Edith Chang’s handwriting) ) (Box 09, Folder 01.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Notes for Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang, [n.p., n.d.], (3 page manuscript (Edith Chang’s handwriting) ) (Box 09, Folder 01.04)
      [Note: With news clippings dated 18 April [1965]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Drafts and Notes for Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang, [n.p., n.d.], (6 Notebooks of 34, 26, ,24, 28, 28 and 8 pages respectively. ) (Box 09, Folder 02.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Drafts and Notes for Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang, [n.p., n.d.], (27 page manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 02.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Drafts and Notes for Translation of The Sure Victory by Mei-ling Soong Chiang, [n.p., n.d.], (29 page manuscript, 6 page notes and 2page separate leafs. ) (Box 09, Folder 02.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Miscellaneous Notes, [n.p., n.d.], (3 page notepaper, and 8 page manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 02.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Translation notes for They Speak by Silence, [n.p., n.d.], (8 page autograph manuscript (b.d.) ) (Box 09, Folder 03)
    - [Unknown] Chinese Translation of They Speak by Silence, [n.p., n.d.], (2 sets of 72 page each ) (Box 09, Folder 03.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Draft for the first 3 chapters of Chinese translation of They Met at Calvary by W. E. Sangster, [n.p., n.d.], (55 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 04.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. English text with Chinese notes for They Met at Calvary by W. E. Sangster, [n.p., n.d.], (104 page, typed manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 04.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Chinese translation draft for They Met at Calvary by W. E. Sangster, [n.p., n.d.], (11 autograph notebooks of 47, 14, 20, 54,56, 48,56, 56, 58, 54, and 25 page respectively as well as 2 page notepaper and 13 separate page autograph manuscript in Notebook 1 and 2 separate page autograph manuscript each in Chinese and English in Notebook 10 ) (Box 09, Folder 04.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Vocabulary Notes on They Met at Calvary by W. E. Sangster, [n.p., n.d.], (34 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 04.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. English text of They Met at Calvary by W. E. Sangster, [n.p., n.d.], (39 page, typed manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 04.05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L.? Copy of William James's "Pragmatism," translated by Meng Xian Zheng [Shanghai: Shang Wu], Yinshuguan, [n.d.], (3 paper bound volumes of 106, 123 and 122 page respectively ) (Box 09, Folder 05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L.? Tang Dynasty Poetry, [n.p.] 1941 (Box 09, Folder 06)
      [Six Chinese old style paper volumes of 75,73, 66, 61, 59, and 75 page respectively.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L.? Tang Dynasty Songs, [n.p., n.d.], (Two Chinese old style paper volumes of 81 and 71 pages respectively. ) (Box 09, Folder 07)
    - H. L. and Edith Chang Poems in Chinese, [n.p., n.d.], (photocopy of one handwritten page ) (Box 09, Folder 08)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Inside Assault on European Puppet (leaders), [n.p., n.d.], (71 sheets (131 p.) manuscript ) (Box 09, Folder 09)
  - Subseries 2.2: Edith Chang
    - Edith Chang Edith Chang’s Writings: Dedication and Lists of works, [Taipei], 1986-1988, (15 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 01.01)
    - Edith Chang Draft of Good News, [Taipei] 1986, (161 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 02)
    - Edith Chang Final version, Draft of Good News, [Taipei] 30 August, 1986, (158 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 03)
    - Edith Chang English Translation of Good News, [Taipei] 1987-1988, (119 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 04)
    - Edith Chang Drafts of New Life - Chapters 1-20, [Taipei] [n.d.], (89 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 05)
    - Edith Chang Drafts of New Life - Chapters 21-40, [Taipei] [1987], (92 page autograph manuscript and 5 bookmarks ) (Box 10, Folder 06)
    - Edith Chang 9 Testimonies at the Women Alliance’s Garment Factory, [Taipei] [1987], (83 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 07)
    - Edith Chang 7 Testimonies at the Prayer Group, [Taipei] [1987-88], (52 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 08.01)
    - Edith Chang Testimonies at the Prayer Group, [Taipei] [1987-1991], (89 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 10, Folder 08.02)
    - Edith Chang Testimony at the Prayer Group, [Taipei] 27 August 1988, (10 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 01)
    - Edith Chang Draft of True Freedom, [Taipei] 13 November 1988, (26 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 02)
    - Edith Chang What Kind of A Person Peter H. L. Chang Is, [Taipei] [1990], (3 page autograph manuscript [photocopy] ) (Box 11, Folder 03)
    - Edith Chang 1991 Draft of Great Mission, [Taipei] 6 June 1991, (107 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 04.01)
    - Edith Chang 1990 draft of Great Mission, [Taipei] 6 June 1990, (7 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 04.02)
    - Edith Chang 1991 draft of Great Mission, [Taipei] 1991, (40 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 04.03)
    - Edith Chang 1991 draft of Great Mission, [Taipei] 1991, (42 page, autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 04.04)
    - Edith Chang Draft of Love and Hate, [Taipei] [1990-91], (63 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 05)
    - Edith Chang Testimony at the Prayer Group, 1991, [Taipei] [1991], (39 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 06)
    - Edith Chang Testimony at the Taipei City Prison, [Taipei] 26 March 1992, (10 page autograph manuscript (photocopy) ) (Box 11, Folder 07)
    - Edith Chang Testimony at the Veteran’s Hospital, 1992, [Taipei] 27 August 1992 - 19 October 1992, (15 autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 08)
      [With misc. notes]
    - Edith Chang My Testimony, [n.p.] 20 February 1994 - 26 June 1994, (2 page, printed document; 8 page autograph manuscript (photocopy) ) (Box 11, Folder 09)
    - Edith Chang Materials for testimony, [Taipei] [v.d.], (203 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 10.01)
    - Edith Chang Materials for testimony, [n.p.] 1989, (News clipping and 1 page printed hymn ) (Box 11, Folder 10.02)
    - Edith Chang On Security and other issues, [Taipei] [n.d.], (10 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Edith Chang Testimony not used, [Taipei] [1987], (126 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Edith Chang Word list, (1 page autograph manuscript and 5 page autograph manuscript (photocopy) ) (Box 11, Folder 13)